[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 5, "question": "Is it possible this could avert a US military strike on Syria?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "possible", "this", "could", "avert", "a", "US", "military", "strike", "on", "Syria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 6, "answer": "It's possible if it's real.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "possible", "if", "it", "'s", "real", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["US", "Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "Is military strike on pause?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "military", "strike", "on", "pause", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "If in fact that happened.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "in", "fact", "that", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Jessica, I can't really get laid around all this, can you try and tell me in simple, plain English where we are in terms of America's position on Syria?", "question_tokens": ["Jessica", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "really", "get", "laid", "around", "all", "this", ",", "can", "you", "try", "and", "tell", "me", "in", "simple", ",", "plain", "English", "where", "we", "are", "in", "terms", "of", "America", "'s", "position", "on", "Syria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "DT", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Well, that is the challenge of the day, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "is", "the", "challenge", "of", "the", "day", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "I mean, here's my -- I suppose my reaction of this which is if you assume that Assad did unleash these chemical weapons slaughtering 400 children and over a thousand adults and his own people, if you take that assumption, why would you trust that kind of man to hand over his weapons and why would America trust Vladimir Putin in all of these?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "here", "'s", "my", "--", "I", "suppose", "my", "reaction", "of", "this", "which", "is", "if", "you", "assume", "that", "Assad", "did", "unleash", "these", "chemical", "weapons", "slaughtering", "400", "children", "and", "over", "a", "thousand", "adults", "and", "his", "own", "people", ",", "if", "you", "take", "that", "assumption", ",", "why", "would", "you", "trust", "that", "kind", "of", "man", "to", "hand", "over", "his", "weapons", "and", "why", "would", "America", "trust", "Vladimir", "Putin", "in", "all", "of", "these", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Well, and isn't it from the question you raised and I think that the most senior official in government are where you are.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "and", "is", "n't", "it", "from", "the", "question", "you", "raised", "and", "I", "think", "that", "the", "most", "senior", "official", "in", "government", "are", "where", "you", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Assad", "Vladimir Putin"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "I just don't believe that's how this all at it was, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "just", "do", "n't", "believe", "that", "'s", "how", "this", "all", "at", "it", "was", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "DT", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "First of all, it's an issue that has been discussed in private for a long time.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "it", "'s", "an", "issue", "that", "has", "been", "discussed", "in", "private", "for", "a", "long", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "I mean, why does this leave the voting position here?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "why", "does", "this", "leave", "the", "voting", "position", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "MD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "What is your view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Well, it underscores the fact that the administration has not come up with any plausible means to prevent another attack while diplomacy like this may very well accomplish that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "underscores", "the", "fact", "that", "the", "administration", "has", "not", "come", "up", "with", "any", "plausible", "means", "to", "prevent", "another", "attack", "while", "diplomacy", "like", "this", "may", "very", "well", "accomplish", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "But of course, public opinion being against something like this isn't necessarily the sole reason why you would choose to do it or not if you're a President of a country like the United States, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "of", "course", ",", "public", "opinion", "being", "against", "something", "like", "this", "is", "n't", "necessarily", "the", "sole", "reason", "why", "you", "would", "choose", "to", "do", "it", "or", "not", "if", "you", "'re", "a", "President", "of", "a", "country", "like", "the", "United", "States", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Well, it's the public that ends up paying for it and the public that ends up bleeding for it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "the", "public", "that", "ends", "up", "paying", "for", "it", "and", "the", "public", "that", "ends", "up", "bleeding", "for", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Can you hear me?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "hear", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "Right, there was an interruption from (inaudible).", "answer_tokens": ["Right", ",", "there", "was", "an", "interruption", "from", "(", "inaudible", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Would you then support military action?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "then", "support", "military", "action", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "Well, of course that's not where we are but the answer is no.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "of", "course", "that", "'s", "not", "where", "we", "are", "but", "the", "answer", "is", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Will there be attacks against American bases in the Middle East if there's an air strike?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "there", "be", "attacks", "against", "American", "bases", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", "if", "there", "'s", "an", "air", "strike", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "You should expect everything.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "should", "expect", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "Is that the sensible way for America to go?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "sensible", "way", "for", "America", "to", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "Frankly, I don't think it is and this is about much more than the use of chemical weapons.", "answer_tokens": ["Frankly", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "is", "and", "this", "is", "about", "much", "more", "than", "the", "use", "of", "chemical", "weapons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "And if the answer is they shouldn't, why is President Obama going along with it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "the", "answer", "is", "they", "should", "n't", ",", "why", "is", "President", "Obama", "going", "along", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Well, look I think he's exploring it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "exploring", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "And what do you make of hearing the likes of Paul Wolfowitz outlining why we should be piling straight back into Syria given what we now know about the reality of Saddam Hussein's non-existent WMD?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "hearing", "the", "likes", "of", "Paul", "Wolfowitz", "outlining", "why", "we", "should", "be", "piling", "straight", "back", "into", "Syria", "given", "what", "we", "now", "know", "about", "the", "reality", "of", "Saddam", "Hussein", "'s", "non-existent", "WMD", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Well, I do think that, you know, history kind of rhymes but it doesn't exactly repeat itself.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "think", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "history", "kind", "of", "rhymes", "but", "it", "does", "n't", "exactly", "repeat", "itself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul Wolfowitz", "Saddam Hussein"], "LOCATION": ["Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Do you think that's a fair criticism?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "'s", "a", "fair", "criticism", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "I think it's a concern we might have.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "concern", "we", "might", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "Is something brand-new that just knocks your socks off?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "something", "brand-new", "that", "just", "knocks", "your", "socks", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Is he still there?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "still", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "Yes, he is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "he", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", ",", "``", "NNP", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Is he inside now?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "inside", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "No, he's in his car and he continually has his hand on his gun and he keep saying, \"Step closer.\"", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "'s", "in", "his", "car", "and", "he", "continually", "has", "his", "hand", "on", "his", "gun", "and", "he", "keep", "saying", ",", "``", "Step", "closer", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Saying step closer and what?", "question_tokens": ["Saying", "step", "closer", "and", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", "NN", "CC", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "And he's going to shoot us.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "shoot", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "Emily Miller, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Emily", "Miller", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Good to be here, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "to", "be", "here", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Emily Miller"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "Tell me what happened?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "My boys (inaudible) second amendment, I'm not conservative.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "boys", "(", "inaudible", ")", "second", "amendment", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "conservative", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "How did you defend yourself against that one guy?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "defend", "yourself", "against", "that", "one", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "I talked him out.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "talked", "him", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "So, why would you prefer to shoot him?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "why", "would", "you", "prefer", "to", "shoot", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "I wouldn't prefer to shoot.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "prefer", "to", "shoot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 387, "question": "2 million times a year in America, and yet I never read any examples, where are they?", "question_tokens": ["2", "million", "times", "a", "year", "in", "America", ",", "and", "yet", "I", "never", "read", "any", "examples", ",", "where", "are", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["LS", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Well, (inaudible) is like -- I mean ...", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "(", "inaudible", ")", "is", "like", "--", "I", "mean", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "When were all these things happening?", "question_tokens": ["When", "were", "all", "these", "things", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Well, obviously, there's a bias in the liberal media against showing these kinds of stories.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "obviously", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "bias", "in", "the", "liberal", "media", "against", "showing", "these", "kinds", "of", "stories", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "So is every paper in America liberal media?", "question_tokens": ["So", "is", "every", "paper", "in", "America", "liberal", "media", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Not my paper Washington.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "my", "paper", "Washington", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "You want to stop people killing each other, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "to", "stop", "people", "killing", "each", "other", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "He doesn't care about the blind people.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "does", "n't", "care", "about", "the", "blind", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Can I talk?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "talk", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "It's something that's going to happen?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "something", "that", "'s", "going", "to", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "It hasn't happened yet.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "has", "n't", "happened", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Do you think blind people are going to accidentally shoot people?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "blind", "people", "are", "going", "to", "accidentally", "shoot", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "It's been fully legal in most states right now and they're not doing it because gun owners are responsible, which they train responsibly, which they store responsibly.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "been", "fully", "legal", "in", "most", "states", "right", "now", "and", "they", "'re", "not", "doing", "it", "because", "gun", "owners", "are", "responsible", ",", "which", "they", "train", "responsibly", ",", "which", "they", "store", "responsibly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "You actually think that we can have responsible blind gun owners?", "question_tokens": ["You", "actually", "think", "that", "we", "can", "have", "responsible", "blind", "gun", "owners", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "I'm going to tell you what.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "tell", "you", "what", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "It is ridiculous?", "question_tokens": ["It", "is", "ridiculous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "Well, the gun lobby (ph) is not -- the gun always now doing that is the disability groups who actually the ones advocating for this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "gun", "lobby", "(", "ph", ")", "is", "not", "--", "the", "gun", "always", "now", "doing", "that", "is", "the", "disability", "groups", "who", "actually", "the", "ones", "advocating", "for", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "Emily Miller"], "LOCATION": ["Washington"]}, "docId": "130909pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "That's not mine, right?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "mine", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "Emily Gets Her Gun But Obama Wants to Take Yours, Emily Miller, the Senior Editor of the Washington Times, good to meet you.", "answer_tokens": ["Emily", "Gets", "Her", "Gun", "But", "Obama", "Wants", "to", "Take", "Yours", ",", "Emily", "Miller", ",", "the", "Senior", "Editor", "of", "the", "Washington", "Times", ",", "good", "to", "meet", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]